TINGNI BIAN

Royal Oak, MI, 48073 | 313-896-8181 | Tingni0407@outlook.com

Education

University of Detroit Mercy-Detroit, MI, US

Sep 2012-Dec 2013

Master of Arts, Financial Economics

Relevant Courses: Economic Analysis of Enterprises, Practical Issues in Financial Economics, Quantitative Foundations of Economics Analysis, Money and Capital Markets, Theory of International Trade

Nanjing University of Information Science & Technology (NUIST)

-Nanjing, Jiangsu, China

Sep 2008-June 2012

Bachelor of Management, Financial Management (Brunch of Accounting School)

Relevant Courses: Statistics, Auditing, Management Accounting, Advanced Financial Accounting, Cost Accounting, Assets Evaluation, International Trade and Settlement, International Finance

Relevant Experience

Taiho Chinese Restaurant Detroit, MI, US

Sep 2012-Present

Customer Service

- -Professionally handle incoming requests from customers and ensure that issues are resolved both promptly and thoroughly
- -Thoroughly and efficiently gather customer information access and fulfill customer needs, educate the customer where applicable to prevent the need for future contacts and document interactions through contact tracking
- -Provide quality service and support in a variety of areas including, but not limited to: billing, placing print orders, and system troubleshooting

Demmel Metal Components (Nanjing) Co.Ltd, Nanjiing, China Accounting Trainee

May 2011-June2011

- -Practiced routine accounting treatments, prepared various financial statements
- -Established tables of accounts assign to proper account
- -Examined financial statements performance with reporting and procedure standards

Jiangsu Tianhonghuaxin Certified Public Accountants Co.Ltd

June 2009-Aug 2009

Auditor Assistant

- -Filled in audited entity's financial statements schedules and notes
- -Checked financial documents, cash account, bank confirmation and stocktaking
- -Assisted upper-level auditors in setting up a realistic audit working papers, audited schedule with the client. Assisted to establish a permanent file.
- -At the end of the audit, drafted and sent closing correspondence, set up follow-up audits, or filed all related paperwork, including the client's response to the audit report.

Awards

2012 NUIST

2011 NUIST 50 years Anniversary Speech Contest (Chinese)

2009 NUIST

2008-2012 NUIST

2008 NUIST

Summary of Skills

The Excellent Graduate

The Third Prize

The Third Prize Scholarship Excellent Student Cardre Outstanding Student

Fluent in Chinese and English Expertise in MS office- Word, Excel, Poweroint Photoshop, Quickbooks

Looking forward to hearing from you!